<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-03-05T23:25:06+00:00</updated><id>https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><entry><title type="html">i wasted time</title><link href="https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2024/i-wasted-time/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="i wasted time"/><published>2024-11-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-11-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2024/i%20wasted%20time</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2024/i-wasted-time/"><![CDATA[<p>i wasted time<br/> shall i get it back<br/> from my good night’s sleep?</p> <p>i may finish the task<br/> and earn some pay<br/> but rob my spark <br/> the very next day</p> <p>this song<br/> won’t last too long<br/> and health will take it’s toll<br/> whom shall i call? <br/> “a hospital.”</p> <p>i give the money <br/> to pay the price<br/> and buy my health back<br/> just enough to live again<br/> why this bargain? <br/> “better learn to prioritize.”</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poem"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[i wasted time shall i get it back from my good night’s sleep? i may finish the task and earn some pay but rob my spark the very next day this song won’t last too long and health will take it’s toll whom shall i call? “a hospital.” i give the money to pay the price and buy my health back just enough to live again why this bargain? “better learn to prioritize.”]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">i want to fall in love again</title><link href="https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2024/i-want-to-fall-in-love-again/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="i want to fall in love again"/><published>2024-11-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-11-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2024/i%20want%20to%20fall%20in%20love%20again</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2024/i-want-to-fall-in-love-again/"><![CDATA[<p>i want to fall in love again <br/> to get hurt,<br/> to split apart and probe<br/> deep in my heart</p> <p>it’s been too long a break;<br/> i want to check<br/> if the cracks have sealed <br/> and the wounds have healed</p> <p>i want a change of battery,<br/> a new replacement,<br/> for the current one<br/> deserves no flattery</p> <p>who’s in charge?<br/> why do they barge?<br/> should i shoulder or shoulder <br/> these responsibilities?</p> <p>what is satisfaction:<br/> the gelifraction<br/> or the lack of action?</p> <p>author my own fate?<br/> is it too late, au fait,<br/> to get my priorities straight?</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poem"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[i want to fall in love again to get hurt, to split apart and probe deep in my heart it’s been too long a break; i want to check if the cracks have sealed and the wounds have healed i want a change of battery, a new replacement, for the current one deserves no flattery who’s in charge? why do they barge? should i shoulder or shoulder these responsibilities? what is satisfaction: the gelifraction or the lack of action? author my own fate? is it too late, au fait, to get my priorities straight?]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">enchantress</title><link href="https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2023/enchantress/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="enchantress"/><published>2023-05-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2023/enchantress</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sohamkorade.github.io/portfolio//portfolio/blog/2023/enchantress/"><![CDATA[<p>(My heart, a locked garden, where your memory blossoms as a forbidden rose. A forgotten page in the book of my youth, eternally bookmarked, but never revisited.)</p> <p>Between its lines, emotions lie in slumber,<br/> Words frozen in time, a longing I still remember,<br/> For within its folded creases, a story remains,<br/> Of unspoken yearnings, where silence reigns.</p> <p>You, a delicate wildfire, dancing far away,<br/> Consuming my thoughts, yet beyond my sway.<br/> Your gaze, like an arrow, pierced through my heart,<br/> Igniting sparks that left me torn apart.</p> <p>She, my first love, my innocent lust,<br/> A tempest of emotions, an ache I trust,<br/> Her eyes, deep pools reflecting starlit skies,<br/> Undone was my heart in her enchanting guise.</p> <p>Alas, I remained a droplet so shy,<br/> Evaporated as time flew by.<br/> Words failed to find their way to my lips,<br/> Silence gripped us like a total eclipse.</p> <p>And so, I hoped for our paths to intertwine,<br/> For her to turn and see, her gaze to align.<br/> Yet in her eyes, I found no reflection of me,<br/> No flicker of recognition, nor curiosity.</p> <p>The mirror of her gaze, a cruel illusion,<br/> Reflecting back my face in silent delusion.<br/> Words take pause, their secrets to keep,<br/> As silence enveloped us in a trance so deep.</p> <p>Fate’s winds blew against my fervent endeavor,<br/> Carving scars on my heart, oh so bittersweet fling!<br/> Like Icarus, hoping to soar higher,<br/> I flapped my wing,<br/> Realized I had no feather,<br/> just bare arms to bring.</p> <p>In awe I stood, witnessing her indifferent stance.<br/> Cracks in the core of my corazón’s expanse,<br/> It was now clear, this was no mere chance.</p> <p>A bridge dismantled, before it even had a chance to form,<br/> Left me drowning, in a river of unanswered storm.</p> <p>Was it a shield, a guard against vulnerability’s call?<br/> A vigilant sentry to the forbidden rose?<br/> Or merely a façade, hiding emotions behind a wall?</p> <p>For in matters of the heart, sometimes silence does speak,<br/> And the doors she closed are the words she chose to leak.</p> <p>I, like a wanderer, sought solace in her eye,<br/> But life moves on, and so must I.<br/> For destines entwined oft their paths do part,<br/> Transient as shooting stars, they dance, then depart.</p> <p>The butterflies that once fluttered,<br/> have vanished without a trace.<br/> The fireworks that once lit up the sky,<br/> are now ashes, smearing my face.</p> <p>That moment, with you by my side,<br/> Life found its meaning, a joy I can’t hide.<br/> Having discovered everything in your captivating chase,<br/> No other longing can hold its sacred space.</p> <p>And as the sun sets on this chapter, into the unknown I stride.<br/> The magic hour, <br/> where light and darkness collide.<br/> Released from the confines of what came before,<br/> A sea of possibilities lies to explore.</p> <p>Amidst this boundless sea, countless fish to find,<br/> The multiverse unveils, infinite visions unwind.<br/> Yet in the corridors inside my teenage heart,<br/> She’ll forever reside, a masterpiece of art.</p> <p>As the vesper casts its glow upon the sky,<br/> I step forward, into the unbeknownst stage.<br/> Your memories, forever my cherished song,<br/> In my heart they reside as I journey along.</p> <p>In the tapestry of time, a tale of regret is spun,<br/> Words eluded me, trapped by hesitation’s shun.<br/> Unspoken sentiments, refusing to escape my grip,<br/> Dear crush of yesteryears, these feelings I let slip.</p> <p>For in silence, my emotions found a clandestine path,<br/> I leave these words as a token, an unspoken aftermath.<br/> But in the ethereal fabric of memories we wove,<br/> You’ll forever be my first, my unrequited love.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="poem"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[(My heart, a locked garden, where your memory blossoms as a forbidden rose. A forgotten page in the book of my youth, eternally bookmarked, but never revisited.) Between its lines, emotions lie in slumber, Words frozen in time, a longing I still remember, For within its folded creases, a story remains, Of unspoken yearnings, where silence reigns. You, a delicate wildfire, dancing far away, Consuming my thoughts, yet beyond my sway. Your gaze, like an arrow, pierced through my heart, Igniting sparks that left me torn apart. She, my first love, my innocent lust, A tempest of emotions, an ache I trust, Her eyes, deep pools reflecting starlit skies, Undone was my heart in her enchanting guise. Alas, I remained a droplet so shy, Evaporated as time flew by. Words failed to find their way to my lips, Silence gripped us like a total eclipse. And so, I hoped for our paths to intertwine, For her to turn and see, her gaze to align. Yet in her eyes, I found no reflection of me, No flicker of recognition, nor curiosity. The mirror of her gaze, a cruel illusion, Reflecting back my face in silent delusion. Words take pause, their secrets to keep, As silence enveloped us in a trance so deep. Fate’s winds blew against my fervent endeavor, Carving scars on my heart, oh so bittersweet fling! Like Icarus, hoping to soar higher, I flapped my wing, Realized I had no feather, just bare arms to bring. In awe I stood, witnessing her indifferent stance. Cracks in the core of my corazón’s expanse, It was now clear, this was no mere chance. A bridge dismantled, before it even had a chance to form, Left me drowning, in a river of unanswered storm. Was it a shield, a guard against vulnerability’s call? A vigilant sentry to the forbidden rose? Or merely a façade, hiding emotions behind a wall? For in matters of the heart, sometimes silence does speak, And the doors she closed are the words she chose to leak. I, like a wanderer, sought solace in her eye, But life moves on, and so must I. For destines entwined oft their paths do part, Transient as shooting stars, they dance, then depart. The butterflies that once fluttered, have vanished without a trace. The fireworks that once lit up the sky, are now ashes, smearing my face. That moment, with you by my side, Life found its meaning, a joy I can’t hide. Having discovered everything in your captivating chase, No other longing can hold its sacred space. And as the sun sets on this chapter, into the unknown I stride. The magic hour, where light and darkness collide. Released from the confines of what came before, A sea of possibilities lies to explore. Amidst this boundless sea, countless fish to find, The multiverse unveils, infinite visions unwind. Yet in the corridors inside my teenage heart, She’ll forever reside, a masterpiece of art. As the vesper casts its glow upon the sky, I step forward, into the unbeknownst stage. Your memories, forever my cherished song, In my heart they reside as I journey along. In the tapestry of time, a tale of regret is spun, Words eluded me, trapped by hesitation’s shun. Unspoken sentiments, refusing to escape my grip, Dear crush of yesteryears, these feelings I let slip. For in silence, my emotions found a clandestine path, I leave these words as a token, an unspoken aftermath. But in the ethereal fabric of memories we wove, You’ll forever be my first, my unrequited love.]]></summary></entry></feed>